123ticket.com 2013-06-09

# Politica de Privacidad | www.telecoming.com

##  PRIVACY POLICY

##  LEGAL ADVICE

This Website has only information purposes and does not constitute a means of providing the services specified therein, for which the user must fill in the Contact Form located on the Website.

The Telecoming Holding, S.L. (hereinafter, the “Company”) is a Spanish company duly registered at the Commercial Register of Madrid, Volume 30763, Sheet 157, Page M-553574, with registered office in Madrid, Torre Europa, Paseo de la Castellana, 95, Floor 16º, and with CIF number B-86616802.

##  PRIVACY POLICYD

####  1\. Personal data protection

The Privacy Policy settled herein has been drafted taking into consideration the Spanish Data Protection Act 15/1999, December 13rd (hereinafter, “LOPD”) and the Recommendations of the Article 29’s European Group, numbers 2/2001, May 17th and 1/1999, February, according to the European Directive 95/46/CE, October 24th.

This Website does not collect any king of personal data, and it does not transfer to third parties such data without the user’s consent.

####  2\. Personal Data supplied voluntarily by User

Personal data requested by the Company to Users will be only those strictly necessary for their identification and regarding the requested service. Such information will be only processed in order to replying their questions and in compliance with the purposes for which they have been collected, which are duly specify in the service chosen by the user.

The user will be duly informed, before the personal data collection, about the issues ruled by the Privacy Policy settled therein, so that the user can provide the Company with his express, precise and unequivocal consent for the collection of his personal data, according to the determined, explicit and legitimate purposes, indicated for each case.

Personal data provided by the user through filling in the Contact Form, or e-mail, will be incorporated into a file belonging to The Telecoming Holding, S.L., which is duly registered before the relevant authority's public register.

####  3\. Browsing data

The browsing data and software necessary for operation of the website employ standard methods to acquire certain transmission details which are implicit in the in the use of Internet communication.

In this category of data are including the following data: IP address or the domain name used by the user connecting to the Web Site, URL address, time and other parameters relating to the operating system and the user's computer.

The referred data is used for the sole purpose of gaining anonymous statistical data on the use of the website and to control the correct operation and is cancelled straight after being processed.

####  4\. Cookies

Under no circumstances are cookies or other similar means used to store information that would allow the user using the website to be identified. The use of cookies or web bugs is reserved for facilitating the access to the website to the user (user’s preferences and navigation guidelines)

The use of session cookies (which are not permanently memorized in the user’s computer and that disappear by closing the browser), in case of being useful, will solely be limited to gather technical information to identify the session with the objective to facilitate the safe exploration and efficiency of the Web.

If the User do not want to allow the use of the referred elements, he would have to configure his computer’s browser to reject cookies and/or cancelling those already existing, and you should disable the Java Script code that is able in the security configuration of the browser.

####  5\. Access, rectification, cancellation and opposition rights

All those interested will be able to practice access, rectification, cancellation and opposition rights, established in article 15 and next of LOPD, or to revoke his consent for the process of personal data, by writing a letter accompanied by a copy of an official document evidencing your identity to The Telecoming Holding, S.L.: Paseo de la Castellana, 95, Torre Europa, Planta 16º, 28046, Madrid, or by an e-mail to [legal@telecoming.com](mailto:legal@telecoming.com).

####  6\. Links

This Privacy Policy only is of application to the Website of The Telecoming Holding, S.L., and therefore, is not guaranteed in the access through links by this Website, not to the links from this site by other webs.

####  7\. Security

The security measures adopted by The Telecoming Holding, S.L. are appropriate to the security level exigible to personal data provided by the user, according to article 9 LOPD.
